umar siddique

Pakistan



umar123siddique@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/umar-siddique-457934169

Summary

I am a talented, ambitious and hardworking person, with skills and experience in back end development abd making REST APIs in ASP.NET using entity frame workcore.

Furthermore, I am adept at handling multiple tasks on a daily basis competently and at working well under pressure.

Recently, I completed BS in computer science from khawaja fareed university of engineering and information techonology and I am now working in a softwere house in rahim yar khan, as a .Net Developer.

Experience



Dotnet Developer

BuiltIn Soft

Aug 2020 - Present (6 months +)



S Work Zone

BuiltIn Soft

Dec 2020 - Present (2 months +)

This project encourages User to discover and post Jobs. The core funcanlitory worries with Cv/Resume and Video(self presentation) uploading module for the candidate, moreover the candidate can find work as for his Location. The Employeer can post positions and select willing canidates who actually appears to be suitable.! The Project is to be deployed in England.

Data Scraping Application

BuiltIn Soft

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020 (3 months)

Data scraping application which is used to scrape data from any or specific web site

S Food Selling web site

BuiltIn Soft

Oct 2020 - Oct 2020 (1 month)

A web site in which user can register as foodiee and buy food from cook which are register on ths web site



Calligraphy sit

BuiltIn Soft

Sep 2020 - Sep 2020 (1 month)

A web site in which admin add his photos of calligraphy and sale them



S Office Mangement System

BuiltIn Soft

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020 (2 months)

Create a solution for office mangment system that keep record of all income and expence of office as well as mange employies of office

Education



khawaja fareed GOVT. P/G collage Rahim yar khan

FSc, Per Engineering 2013 - 2015



Kwaja fareed university of enginering and information techonology rahim yar khan

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science 2015 - 2019

Skills

Microsoft SQL Server • NopCommerce • ASP.NET MVC • ASP.NET Core • REST APIs